{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":2481,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":21,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Title_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_1","title":"Introduction to Coaching ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5182","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":6},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5182"}}},{"id":"si24453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_2","title":"Objectives ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"Evaluate the importance of body language ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Analyse the levels of listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"Discuss the skills of a coach ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Differentiate between coaching and mentoring ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24350","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_4","Text_Caption_5","Text_Caption_6","Text_Caption_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24350"}}},{"id":"Person_01_Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Person_01_Button_5","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27556","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27565","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Psy_static","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Psy_static","roles":{}},{"id":"Animation_Psy","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Animation_Psy","roles":{}},{"id":"Person_04_Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Person_04_Button_2","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27412","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"coach_static","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"coach_static","roles":{}},{"id":"Animation_coach","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Animation_coach","roles":{}},{"id":"Person_02_Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Person_02_Button_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27505","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"mentor_static","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"mentor_static","roles":{}},{"id":"Animation_mentoor","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Animation_mentoor","roles":{}},{"id":"Content_1_Bg_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Content_1_Bg_9","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Content_1_Text_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Content_1_Text_33","title":"I am a psychologist. I help people with a variety of problems ranging from anxiety and depression to mental health conditions and overcoming traumas.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Content_4_Bg_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Content_4_Bg_6","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Content_4_Text_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Content_4_Text_27","title":"I am a coach. I use my ability to listen, to question and to play back what people tell me to help them clarify what matters to them and help them find solutions for themselves.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Click/Touch a  person to view more ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Content_2_Text_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Content_2_Text_31","title":"I have a lot of experience and I am eager to share. When people ask for advice, I point them out in the right direction using hindsight. I act as a Mentor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27693","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Psy_static","Animation_Psy","coach_static","Animation_coach","mentor_static","Animation_mentoor","Content_1_Text_33","Content_4_Text_27","Content_2_Text_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":240},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27693"}}},{"id":"si24516","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_3","title":"Guess who is who? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"Mentor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Psychologist ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"Coach ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_11","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_12","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_14","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"Drag  and drop the button on the correct picture ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_2","title":"There is no right and wrong.  You cannot determine who is who just by looking at the appearance ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"There is no right and wrong.  You cannot determine who is who just by looking at the appearance ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24653","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide24430","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_8","Text_Caption_9","Text_Caption_10","Image_11","Image_12","Image_14","Text_Caption_11","Failure_Shape_2","Success_Shape_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24430"},"dragDrop":{"sources":[24566,24575,24584],"targets":[24622,24628,24640]}}},{"id":"si25248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_7","title":"Guess who is who? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"Mentor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"Psychologist ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"Coach ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Drag  and drop the button on the correct box ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"Someone who has  experience and can be trusted to share his/her expertise  and guidance supported by  hindsight. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"Someone who may or may not have  expertise and acts as a guide to draw out the best in people. The primary focus is the present and future. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"Someone who received specialised training and gained  experitise in healthy communication, parenting and social skills as well as mental, emotional and psychological health. The primary focus is the past and the present.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_3","title":"Are you sure?  Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_3","title":"Well done ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","roles":{}},{"id":"si34044","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide25247","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_16","Text_Caption_17","Text_Caption_18","Text_Caption_19","Text_Caption_20","Text_Caption_21","Text_Caption_22","Failure_Shape_3","Success_Shape_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":270},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25247"},"dragDrop":{"sources":[25121,25129,25137],"targets":[25273,25285,25294]}}},{"id":"si34313","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34132","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Match the roles with the statements. Consider ‘driving a car’ as a methaphor, who will... ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34163","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34167","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Share tips from the experience of driving cars ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Encourage and support you  in driving the car ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34205","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Explore what is stopping you from driving the car ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34173","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34177","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Coach ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34177ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Coach","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34194","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Mentor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34198ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mentor","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34215","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34219","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Psychologist ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34219ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Psychologist","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34263","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34299","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34071q0","for":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34324","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quick Check  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34071q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34071","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si34132","si34177","si34198","si34219","si34299","si34324","si34250"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34071"},"question":{"interactionId":"34095","quizId":377,"title":"Quick Check\r","text":"Match the roles with the statements. Consider ‘driving a car’ as a methaphor, who will...\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si27263","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"InteractiveWidget_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"InteractiveWidget_3","roles":{"interaction":{"type":"Not implemented","title":"Not implemented","categories":[]}}},{"id":"Slide27262","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["InteractiveWidget_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27262"}}},{"id":"Widget_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Widget_1","roles":{"interaction":{"type":"Not implemented","title":"Not implemented","categories":[]}}},{"id":"Slide26943","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Widget_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26943"}}},{"id":"si29826","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_14","title":"Skills of a good coach ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_9","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"Listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_10","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"Observing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_8","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"Reflecting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_13","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Feedbacking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_11","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"Questioning ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_12","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"People skills ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_14","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"Encouraging ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_15","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Goal-setting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si37605","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si37631","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide29803","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_102","Text_Caption_103","Text_Caption_104","Text_Caption_107","Text_Caption_105","Text_Caption_108","Text_Caption_109","Text_Caption_106","Button_11","si37605","si37631"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":270},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide29803"}}},{"id":"si37676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_15","title":"Quiz: Which is not a skill of a coach Choose the correct one by tapping/clicking. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_110","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_66","title":"Questioning ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_111","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":"Instructing ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_112","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_68","title":"Encouraging ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_113","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_69","title":"Observing ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Click_Box_3q1"},"question":{"interactionId":"37894","quizId":377,"text":"NA","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_9","title":"Correct. A coach is merely a guide, instructing/telling might be a good skill for a mentor, but  it is not a skill for a coach  Click anywhere ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Click_Box_3q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_9","title":"Sorry. The correct answer was instructing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Click_Box_3q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide37632","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_110","Image_111","Image_112","Image_113","Click_Box_3","Success_Shape_9","Failure_Shape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide37632"}}},{"id":"si30135","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35358","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True or False? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30169","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The most important skill of a coach is listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30184_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30195","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30199","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30195_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30229","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30125q2","for":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30203","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30216","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31011","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct. Listening is the most important skill.  - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30125q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide30125","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si30162","si30169","si30188","si30199","si30229","si30203","si30216"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30125"},"question":{"interactionId":"30149","quizId":377,"title":"True or False?\r","text":"The most important skill of a coach is listening\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si29685","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_13","title":"The levels of listening ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"Listening with a divided attention ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"Listening, waiting to speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"Listening to disagree ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"Listening to understand ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"Pretend to listen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"Not Listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"Empathic listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_1","roles":{}},{"id":"SVG_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_3","roles":{}},{"id":"SVG_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_7","roles":{}},{"id":"SVG_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_5","roles":{}},{"id":"SVG_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_6","roles":{}},{"id":"SVG_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_4","roles":{}},{"id":"SVG_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si36697","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si36711","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide29579","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_60","Text_Caption_61","Text_Caption_62","Text_Caption_63","Text_Caption_64","Text_Caption_65","Text_Caption_66","Button_10","si36697","si36711"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":342},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide29579"}}},{"id":"si33157","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35367","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33191","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Someone wants to speak to you. You are on the phone, but on hold, and decide to listen. This is an example of: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33206","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accurate Listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33206_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Accurate Listening\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33217","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33221","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Pretending to Listen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33217_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pretending to Listen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33325","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Listening with a divided attention ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33321_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening with a divided attention\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33336","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33340","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Listening waiting to speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33336_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening waiting to speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33264","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si33300","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33147q3","for":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33238","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Whilst you may be partly listening, you’re actually focusing on the phone. - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33937","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33147q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33147","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si33184","si33191","si33210","si33221","si33325","si33340","si33300","si33937"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33147"},"question":{"interactionId":"33171","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Someone wants to speak to you. You are on the phone, but on hold, and decide to listen. This is an example of:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si33623","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","roles":{}},{"id":"si33386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"Your partner is telling you about his/her day, whilst you are watching your favourite TV show. You nod and say ‘uh-hum’ every now and then. This is an example of: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"Not Listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33409_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Not Listening\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"Pretending to Listen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33420_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pretending to Listen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33431","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Listening with a divided attention ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33431_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening with a divided attention\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33442","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"Listening waiting to speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33442_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening waiting to speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33612","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33622q4","for":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere  to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33950","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Nodding and occasional “uh-hums” whilst actually focusing on something else is a typical example  of pretending to listen. - Click anywhere to continue.. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33622q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33622","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si33386","si33398","si33413","si33424","si33435","si33446","si33612","si33546"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33622"},"question":{"interactionId":"33366","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Your partner is telling you about his/her day, whilst you are watching your favourite TV show. You nod and say ‘uh-hum’ every now and then. This is an example of:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si33913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35385","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","roles":{}},{"id":"si33676","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33688","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"In a conversation someone said something very interesting but with no signs of stopping. You already have 2 questions but you  prefer not interrupting. This is an example of: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33699","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33703","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"Listening with a divided attention ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33699_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"11_18","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening with a divided attention\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"Listening waiting to speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33710_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening waiting to speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33721","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33725","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"Listening to disagree ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33721_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening to disagree\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33736","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"Listening Empathically ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33732_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Listening Empathically\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33902","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33912q5","for":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33836","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33963","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct, whilst it is polite to not interrupt, you are effectively waiting to speak - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33912q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33912","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si33676","si33688","si33703","si33714","si33725","si33736","si33902","si33836"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33912"},"question":{"interactionId":"33656","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"In a conversation someone said something very interesting but with no signs of stopping. You already have 2 questions but you  prefer not interrupting. This is an example of:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si38227","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39268","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_78","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39280","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_80","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39324","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_81","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39312","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_17","title":"Observing Albert Mehrabian’s model (click for more details)  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_7","title":"In a conversation, our feelings and attitudes are conveyed with: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SVG_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SVG_16","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"Body Language  55% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"Voice 38% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"Words 7% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"contentvoice","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"contentvoice","title":"Voice includes: - Tone - Pitch - Rate - Volume - Emphasis - silences ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"contentbody","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"contentbody","title":"Body Language includes: - facial expressions - hand gestures - body posture - touch - use of space ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"contentwords","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"contentwords","title":"Both spoken and unspoken ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38183","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_120","Text_Caption_121","Text_Caption_122"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38183"}}},{"id":"si38454","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_18","title":"Want more details? Check out the Secrets of Body Language documentary ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Widget_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Widget_2","roles":{"interaction":{"type":"Not implemented","title":"Not implemented","categories":[]}}},{"id":"Slide38410","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Widget_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38410"}}},{"id":"si38083","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_16","title":"Observing/paying attention Which photo express Anger (touch or click) ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_119","roles":{}},{"id":"Click_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Click_Box_5q6"},"question":{"interactionId":"39916","quizId":377,"text":"NA","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_10","title":"Correct ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Click_Box_5q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_10","title":"Sorry the bottom-middle one was the correct answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Click_Box_5q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38055","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_119","Click_Box_5","Success_Shape_10","Failure_Shape_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38055"}}},{"id":"si39633","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39623q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39644","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39623q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Observing/paying attention one sentence, several  meanings ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Based on the emphasis on the underlined word, which of  these sentences implies that you did not tell John,  but  you  may  have told someone else? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39691","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39695","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I did not tell John you were responsible ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39691_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I did not tell John you were responsible\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39706","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I did not tell John you were responsible ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39702_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I did not tell John you were responsible\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39855","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I did not tell John you were responsible ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39851_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I did not tell John you were responsible\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si39866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39870","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I did not tell John you were responsible ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39866_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I did not tell John you were responsible\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si39749","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si39785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide39623q7","for":"Slide39623q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39710","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39623q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39623q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si39736","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide39623q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide39623","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si39669","si39676","si39695","si39706","si39855","si39870","si39785","si39736"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide39623"},"question":{"interactionId":"39656","quizId":377,"title":"Observing/paying attention\rone sentence, several  meanings\r","text":"Based on the emphasis on the underlined word, which of  these sentences implies that you did not tell John,  but  you  may  have told someone else?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si31877","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40061","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si40069","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si31888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31943","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si31947","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40057","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si40065","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide31867","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide31867"}}},{"id":"si39371","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_19","title":"Thank You ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":"Next time.... the GROW model ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide39343","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_125"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide39343"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Kumon-CoachingRC1","class":"project","title":"Kumon-CoachingRC1","children":["Slide5182","Slide24350","Slide27693","Slide24430","Slide25247","Slide34071","Slide27262","Slide26943","Slide29803","Slide37632","Slide30125","Slide29579","Slide33147","Slide33622","Slide33912","Slide38183","Slide38410","Slide38055","Slide39623","Slide31867","Slide39343"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["Slide34071q0","Click_Box_3q1","Slide30125q2","Slide33147q3","Slide33622q4","Slide33912q5","Click_Box_5q6","Slide39623q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":70,"passScore":56}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5182","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide24350","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide27693","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide24430","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide25247","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide34071","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide27262","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide26943","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide29803","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide37632","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide30125","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide29579","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide33147","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide33622","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide33912","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide38183","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide38410","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide38055","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide39623","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide31867","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide39343","title":"Slide 21"}]}